#### SUMMARY

I am a Full Stack Web Developer hungry to learn as much as possible and grow professionally. I am passionate about creating products that are intuitive and rewarding to use.

I have experience working with multiple libraries and frameworks and I'm familiar with many development methodologies such as Test Driven Development, Agile Development and Scrum.

I'm highly adaptable, I take ownership of my work and I am excited for any opportunity to learn and grow as a Web Developer.

In my spare time, I am also an avid tabletop and video gamer with a soft spot for deck-building games.

## CONTACT

trevorspears.com

**9** Greater Seattle Area

in trevorspears

**O** tgspears

# **EDUCATION**

General Assembly Certificate Web Development Immersive 2015

Seattle Central Community College Programming July 2014 - March 2015

Edmonds Community College August 2008 - February 2010

#### **SKILLS**

LANGUAGES: Ruby, Javascript, HTML5, CSS3

FRAMEWORKS: Rails, Express.js, AngularJS, Node.j, Sails.js

**DATABASE TOOLS:** PostgreSQL, MongoDB

TESTING: Rspec, TDD

OTHER TECHNOLOGIES: Bootstrap, Git/Github, jQuery, Heroku, AJAX, JSON,

APIs, Windows, Linux

PROFESSIONAL: Quick-learner, Diligent, Self-starter, Curious, Adaptable,

Problem-solver

# **EMPLOYMENT**

## Fullstack Web Developer Freelancer & Contractor

Seattle, WA Jun 2015 to Current

Partnering with one other developer to build a redesigned, mobile responsive website for Paramount Life & General Insurance Corp. We built an external API to serve up product data and integrated a content management system (Refinery CMS) across the site. UI development work includes jQuery and CSS3 animations to enhance interaction design. Technologies also include Ruby on Rails, postgreSQL, SASS and Javascript.

# General Assembly

Seattle, WA

Web Development Immersive Student Mar 2015 to Jun 2015 Full-time web development student for an intensive, immersive coding program with complete commitment for 70+ hours a week with a focus on learning and using Ruby on Rails and the MEAN stack. Participated in and attended full-day lectures and coding labs. Built full-scale apps both individually and in group projects.

## Perfect Image

Kirkland, WA Feb 2013 to Aug 2013

Digital Archiving Associate

Responsible for digital archiving of printed and microfiche documents, including extensive indexing. Familiar with AutoScan, Image Capture Plus &

Adobe softwares.

### Nintendo of America

Kirkland, WA

Materials Management Shipping Associate Apr 2010 to Oct 2012 Responsible for readying Nintendo products for shipment to various vendors. Ensured safe and proper product packaging, palletizing, and accurate creation of shipping manifests. Assisted in maintaining efficient team work-flow in a fast-paced environment.